{
    "id": "35e688d17b384670b569f525dfaaedc2",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The striking workers have decided to ……………………….. the meeting for an indefinite period.",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone.",
            "answers": [
                "put down",
                "put off",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The President ………………………… the leader of the party that won the most seats to form the government.",
            "description": "To call upon is to invite.",
            "answers": [
                "called in",
                "called out",
                "called upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager is faced with more problems than he can easily ………………………..",
            "description": "To get over is to overcome.",
            "answers": [
                "get over",
                "get across",
                "get out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor advised the patient to …………………………….. smoking.",
            "description": "To give up is to stop.",
            "answers": [
                "give up",
                "give in",
                "give out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The travelers …………………………. very early in the morning.",
            "description": "To get up is to rise from bed.",
            "answers": [
                "got out",
                "got up",
                "got in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The patient had ………………………….. before the doctor arrived.",
            "description": "To pass away is to die. ",
            "answers": [
                "passed out",
                "passed off",
                "passed away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He faced his enemy bravely but in the end he had to ……………………….",
            "description": "To give in is to surrender.",
            "answers": [
                "give out",
                "give in",
                "give off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The job will …………………………… very little of your time.",
            "description": "To take up is to consume or occupy.",
            "answers": [
                "take out",
                "take in",
                "take up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ………………………… the files carefully.",
            "description": "To go through is to examine.",
            "answers": [
                "go through",
                "go after",
                "get through"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The firemen worked hard for hours to ……………………….. the fire in the factory.",
            "description": "To put out is to extinguish.",
            "answers": [
                "put off",
                "put out",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was his carelessness that ……………………………. the accident.",
            "description": "To bring something about is to cause it to happen.",
            "answers": [
                "brought about",
                "brought out",
                "brought up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came over",
                "came out",
                "came across"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}